

#### **SKILLS**

 $\label{eq:html} \begin{aligned} & \mathsf{HTML} \cdot \mathsf{CSS} \cdot \mathsf{JavaScript} \cdot \mathsf{Ruby} \cdot \\ & \mathsf{Ruby} \ \mathsf{on} \ \mathsf{Rails} \cdot \mathsf{SQL} \cdot \mathsf{Figma} \cdot \mathsf{React} \cdot \\ & \mathsf{Vue} \cdot \mathsf{GitHub} \cdot \mathsf{Heroku} \end{aligned}$ 

### **LANGUAGES**

German Native •••••

English Proficient •••••

Spanish Beginner •••••

### **STRENGTHS**



Flexibility

Communication

🔥 Adaptability

## ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Website Project

- Currently designing and developing a professional website for a freelance client
- focusing on user experience and visual appeal using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

# NICOLE BESEL

## Full Stack Developer

49 171 3323800 @ nicole.besel@gmx.de

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-besel/ https://github.com/nicole-be

Hamburg, Germany

#### **PROFILE**

Junior Full Stack Developer with a background in media. Recently graduated from Le Wagon intensive **Web Development Bootcamp** and completed a group project building a website recommending movies to users. My **passion for frontend development**, coupled with media background, enables me to deliver engaging digital experiences that resonate with users. Looking forward to contributing to your team's success.

#### **EDUCATION**

Apprenticeship as Media Assistant Secondary School of Economics

Huss-Verlag GmbH, Munich Wirtschaftsschule Breitschaft, Regensburg

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Web Development

12/2023 - 02/2024

## Le Wagon

- 10-week full-time intensive coding bootcamp
- Learned and used HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SQL, Git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails
- Designed, implemented and shipped two web apps to production

Trip abroad 03/2021 - 10/2023

Latin America, Asia, Australasia

HR administrator 11/2018 - 06/2019
Univativ Hamburg

Team Assistant 10/2017 - 11/2018 Emotion Hamburg

Front Desk Receptionist

JOM Operational Media

O4/2017 - 10/2017

Hamburg

## **PROJECTS**



## MovieMojo

Automated Movie suggestion Web app for recommending movies based on users preferences. In a team of 4, we used Ruby on Rails, APIs, JavaScript and more. Further development planned: improving our algorithm for better film recommendations.



#### HelPet

Online platform designed to arrange a temporary companionship with emotional support pets. Users can rent a pet or create a profile of their pets and search for location or specific animal.